investia.info 2009-06-27

# Investia | Get Paid Over And Over

**Investia** understands that privacy is important to users, especially when conducting business. This privacy policy regards how we store and deal with your user information.

As a registered user at **Investia** , you have confirmed to have read and understood to the following terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy is divided in the following areas.

**1\. PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
**1.1** **Investia** may collect basic user profile information from all visitors.

**1.2** In addition, third party services may collect information from Investia visitors and registered users . This website does not control how these third parties use such information. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them.

**1.3** **Investia** uses Personal Identifiable Information to customize their site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. **Investia** may e-mail visitors and registered users about research or purchase and sending information related to the subject matter of its business. **Investia** may also use this information to contact visitors and users in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information.

**1.4** Personal Identifiable Information collected by **Investia** is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees, except for use as indicated above. **Investia** audits its security systems and processes on a regular basis. However, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors and break-ins, **Investia** cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place.

**2\. COOKIES**  
**2.1** Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. Investia uses Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of Visitors and the services they select. **Investia** also uses Cookies for security purposes to protect Authorized Customers. 

**2.2** **Investia** uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.

**3\. OTHERS**  
**3.1** **Investia** will publish any changes to the privacy policy by posting such changes on its site. However, if **Investia** website is changing the privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personal Identifiable Information that a registered user has previously requested not be disclosed, this website will contact such user via e-mail to notify these changes.

**3.2** **Investia** contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. **Investia** encourages you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from us.
